Finding aid for the Xavier University Alumni Association records
Xavier University Archives and Special Collections
Xavier University Alumni Association records
1870-2010
Xavier University Archives and Special Collections Phone: 513-745-4821 http://www.xavier.edu/cm/archives
Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). Alumni Association
7 linear feet (14 boxes)
This is a collection of various records of the Xavier University Alumni Association and of the Xavier University Alumnae Association. Prior to 1930 Xavier University was known as St. Xavier College. Types of information include administrative materials, alumni listings, and event information.
XUA-38
History of Xavier University Alumni Association
The St. Xavier College (later Xavier University) Alumni Association was formed in 1888. The Alumnae Association began in 1926 and merged with the Alumni Association in 1973. The purpose of the organization has been to financially support the university through fund raising and organizational events.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of administrative records, alumni listings, events and activities information, and other information.
Statement of Arrangement
This collection is arranged into series:
Administration
Alumni Listings
Events/Activities
Photographs, Miscellaneous,and Affiliations
Alumnae Association Records
Oversized Materials and Volumes
Restrictions on Access
Restricted access. Please contact the Xavier University archives staff.
Accruals
XUA2017-009
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Subjects:
Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio)--Alumni and alumnae; Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio)--Alumni and alumnae--Societies, etc.
Organizations/Corporations:
Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). Alumnae Association
Detailed Description of The Collection
- Administration, 1889-2010
  - Constitution and By-Laws, 1889-2009
    - Constitution, 1889 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      "Constitution and By-Laws of the Alumni Association of St. Xavier College"
    - Constitution, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      "Constitution and By-Laws: St. Xavier Alumni Association"
    - Constitution, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      "Constitution and By-Laws with Amendments: Xavier University Alumni Association"
    - Constitution, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      "Proposed Revision of the Constitution of the Xavier University Alumni Association"
    - Constitution, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      "The Constitution of the Xavier University Alumni Association"
    - Constitution, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      "Xavier University National Alumni Association Constitution and By-Laws"
    - Constitution, Undated [2000s?] (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Membership cards, 1941; 1948
    - Membership cards, 1942; 1948 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      Association membership cards.
  - Association Officers, 1914-2010; undated
    - Officers, 1914-2000; undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
      Lists of officers of the Alumni Association, newspaper reports on their election and miscellaneous election papers.
  - Committees, 1896-1977
    - Board of Governors, 1886-1903 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      Minutes and papers of the committees of the Alumni Association, primarily the Board of Governors. Note: 1896 minutes are represented by a typed extract only.
    - Board of Governors, 1920-1925 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      Minutes and papers of the committees of the Alumni Association, primarily the Board of Governors.
    - Board of Governors, 1931-1935 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Board of Governors, 1936-1939 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      Minutes and papers of the Alumni Association, primarily the Board of Governors.
    - Board of Governors, 1940-1946 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Board of Governors, 1947-1949 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Board of Governors, 1950-1959 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Board of Governors, 1960-1969 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      Minutes and papers of the committees of the Alumni Association, primarily the Board of Governors
    - Board of Governors, 1971-1973 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Board of Governors, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Board of Governors, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Membership Committee, 1905-1960 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      Papers and correspondence relating to the Membership Committee.
    - House Committee, 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      Papers and correspondence relating to the House Committee
    - Athletic Advisory Committee, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      Papers and correspondence relating to the Athletic Advisory Committee.
  - Reports, 1929; 1962-1968; undated
    Reports of the Association's activities for the year 1929, 1961-1962, 1966-1967, and 1967-1968.
    - Reports: Annual, 1929; 1962-1968; undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Reports: Historian's Report, 1894 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      "Report of the Historian of the St. Xavier Alumni Association" reporting on the year's activities, and providing a brief outline of the early years of St. Xavier College.
    - Reports: 70th Anniversary History, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      A report on the history and activities of the Alumni Association on the occasion of its 70th anniversary.
    - Reports: College History, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      A brief history of Xavier University, delivered by Edward VonderHaar, Director of Publicity and Alumni Secretary.
    - Report, undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
      Page from an undated report about the activities of the Association
  - Publications, 1963-1968
    - Publications, 1963-1968 (Box 2, Folder 29)
      Photocopies of "Alumni Chapter News" (January and February 1963) and "XU Alumni Briefs" (October, 1968)
    - Publications: Alumni Guidebook, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      Alumni Guidebook, outlining the purpose, activities and personnel of the Alumni Association.
    - Alumni Publications Survey, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 31)
      Results of a survey sent to other universities requesting information on their alumni publications.
  - Local Chapters, 1934-2010
    - Chapter Officers and Membership, 1961-2010 (Box 3, Folder 32)
      Details of local chapter leaders and membership numbers
    - Chapter Policies and Procedures, 1962-1970 (Box 3, Folder 33)
      Alumni Chapter Policies and Procedures manual (1970); example constitution for a local chapter (undated); Fort Sill charter of membership as an official chapter of the Xavier University Alumni Association (January 1962)
    - Chapter: New York, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 34)
      Policies and correspondence relating to the New York alumni association chapter.
    - Chapter: Chicago, 1935-1947 (Box 3, Folder 35)
      Papers and correspondence relating to the Chicago alumni association chapter.
    - Chapter: Louisville, 1940-1970 (Box 3, Folder 36)
      Papers and correspondence relating to the Louisville alumni association chapter, including the constitution and annual reports.
    - Chapter: Washington, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 37)
      Papers and correspondence relating to the Washington alumni association chapter.
    - Chapter: Cleveland, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 38)
      Papers relating to the Cleveland alumni association chapter.
    - Chapter: Fort Wayne, undated [1950s] (Box 3, Folder 39)
      Fort Wayne Xavier Club constitution.
  - Finances, 1933-1992
    - Finances: Banking Records, 1917-1918 (Box 3, Folder 40)
      Bank statements and cashed checks
    - Finances: Living Endowment Fund, 1956-1974 (Box 3, Folder 41)
      Papers relating to the Living Endowment Fund (1956-1968), including Honor Rolls of those who have contributed (1953-1961,1971).
    - Finances: University Advancement Fund, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 42)
      Results of an alumni survey in preparation for launch of University Advancement Fund.
    - Finances: Fundraising Misc., 1933-1992 (Box 3, Folder 43)
      Papers and correspondence relating to various fundraising efforts.
  - Correspondence-Miscellaneous, 1904-1974
  - Correspondence -Miscellaneous, 1904-1974
    Letters and memoranda to and from the Alumni Association covering various topics, including the need for a school song.
- Alumni Listings, 1884-1994
  - Class Lists, 1870-1990
    - Class Lists, 1884-1899 (Box 3, Folder 45)
      List of class members as of March 20, 1949
    - Class Lists, 1901-1909 (Box 3, Folder 46)
      List of class members as of March 20, 1949.
    - Class Lists, 1910-1919 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Class Lists, 1920-1929 (Box 4, Folder 48)
      Lists of class members as of March 20, 1949
    - Class Lists, 1930-1936 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Class Lists, 1944-1949 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Class Lists, 1870-1899 (Box 4, Folder 51)
      Lists of class members; date compiled not known.
    - Class Lists, 1900-1919 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Class Lists, 1920-1929 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Class Lists, 1930-1936 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Class Lists, 1940-1951 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Class Rosters, 1893-1956 (Box 5, Folder 56)
      Class rosters.
  - Class Directories, 1944-1994
    - Class Directories, 1944-1994 (Box 5, Folder 57)
      25th and 50th anniversary directories for the class of 1929; 25th anniversary directory for the class of 1948; directory for Charter Class I (May 1994)
  - General Alumni Listings, Undated
    - Alumni Listing, undated [1900?] (Box 5, Folder 59)
      "Alumni Listing": a series of directories listing names alphabetically with address: Directory No. 2 Alumni Association; Directory No.4 Postgraduate and Lyceum & Varia; Directory No. 5 Patrons and Friends of College.
    - Alumni Listing, Undated [1930s?] (Box 5, Folder 60)
      "Alumni Listing"; unbound notebook listing names alphabetically with address and reference number.
  - Alumni with MD, 1949-1955
    - Alumni with M.D., 1949-1955 (Box 5, Folder 61)
      Listings of Doctors of Medicine in the Alumni Association
  - Alumni with Doctorates, 1983
    - Alumni with doctorates, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 62)
      Listings of alumni with Doctorate Degrees (current to c.1983).
  - Clergy Alumni, 1840-1942
    - Alumni Clergy, 1840-1942 (Box 5, Folder 63)
      Listings of clergy who attended Xavier.
  - Prominent Alumni, undated [1930?]-1990
    - Prominent Alumni, undated [1930?]-1990 (Box 5, Folder 64)
      Listings of prominent Xavier graduates, including leaders in law, medicine, architecture, education and business (1971); alumni in the U.S. Congress (1990); biographies of sales executive John B. Naughton (undated (1971?) and journalist Junius Henri Brown (Undated [1930?]; newspaper clippings concerning alumni Dr. Thomas P. Hart, Rev. Theodore H. Rolfes, J. Donald Barman, Joseph Link Jr., and Bishop Harold W. Henry (undated, 1937-1960); World World Two veteran Tom Broderick, as a chapter in the book The Greatest Generation by Tom Brokaw.
  - Class Agents, 1886-1951
    - Class Agents, 1890-1951 (Box 5, Folder 65)
      Listings of class agents and representatives
  - Miscellaneous, 1930-1953; undated
    - Alumni Listings: Miscellaneous, 1930-1953; undated (Box 5, Folder 66)
      Miscellaneous listings of uncertain purpose (undated); plus graduates interested in teaching (1930); alumni on faculty (undated); alumni in the Columbus and Cleveland areas (1953); members of the Ohio College Association (undated).
- Events and Activities, 1889-2010
  - Alumni Association 75th Anniversary, 1963
    - Alumni Association 75th Anniversary, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 67)
      Papers and correspondence relating to the 75th Anniversary celebrations of the founding of the Alumni Association.
    - Alumni Association 75th Anniversary, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 68)
      Event programs for the Alumni Association 75th Anniversary celebrations.
  - Homecoming, 1930-2010
    Programs and other publicity material for annual Homecoming events.
    - Homecoming, 1930; 1938; 1939 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - Homecoming, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - Homecoming, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Homecoming, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - Homecoming, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - Homecoming, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - Homecoming, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - Homecoming, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - Homecoming, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - Homecoming, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 78)
    - Homecoming, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 79)
    - Homecoming, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 80)
    - Homecoming, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - Homecoming, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - Homecoming, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 83)
    - Homecoming, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - Homecoming, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Homecoming, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 86)
    - Homecoming, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 87)
    - Homecoming, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 88)
    - Homecoming, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 89)
    - Homecoming, 1971; 1972; 1977 (Box 6, Folder 90)
    - Homecoming, 1983; 1988; 1989 (Box 6, Folder 91)
    - Homecoming, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 92)
    - Homecoming, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 93)
    - Homecoming, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 94)
    - Homecoming, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 95)
    - Homecoming, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 96)
    - Homecoming, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 97)
    - Homecoming, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 98)
    - Homecoming, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 99)
    - Homecoming, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 100)
    - Homecoming, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 101)
    - Homecoming, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 102)
    - Homecoming, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 103)
  - Reunions, 1954-2000
    - Reunion: Class of 1929, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 104)
      Programs and other publicity material for the reunion of the class of 1929
    - Reunion: Class of 1904, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 105)
      50th Anniversary Testimonial certificate presented to the class of 1904 on the occasion of the Testimonial Breakfast, June 5, 1954.
    - Reunion: Class of 1930, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 106)
      Programs and other publicity material for class specific reunions: Class of 1930
    - Reunion: Class of 1941, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 107)
      Programs and other publicity material for class specific reunions: Class of 1941
    - Reunion: Class of 1931, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 108)
      Programs and other publicity material for class specific reunions: Class of 1931.
    - Reunion: Class of 1932, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 109)
      Programs and other publicity material for class specific reunions: Class of 1932.
    - Reunion: Class of 1933, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 110)
      Programs and other publicity material for class specific reunions: Class of 1933
    - Reunion: Class of 1908, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 111)
      50th Anniversary Testimonial certificate presented to the class of 1908 on the occasion of the Testimonial Breakfast, June 5, 1958.
    - Reunion: Class of 1943, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 112)
      Programs and other publicity material for class specific reunions: Class of 1943
    - Reunion: Class of 1935, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 113)
      Programs and other publicity material for class specific reunions: Class of 1935
    - Reunion: Class of 1936, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 114)
      Programs and other publicity material for class specific reunions: Class of 1936
    - Reunion: Class of 1950, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 115)
      Programs and other publicity material for class specific reunions: Class of 1950
    - Reunion: Class of 1928, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 116)
      Programs and other publicity material for class specific reunions: Class of 1928
    - Reunion: Class of 1954, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 117)
      Programs and other publicity material for class specific reunions: Class of 1954
    - Reunion: Class of 1955, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 118)
      Programs and other publicity material for class specific reunions: Class of 1955
    - Reunion: Class of 1935, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 119)
    - Reunion: Class of 1942, undated [1977?] (Box 7, Folder 120)
      Programs and other publicity material for class specific reunions: Class of 1942
    - Reunions: Miscellaneous, 1954; 1962; 1999; 2000 (Box 7, Folder 121)
      Publicity materials of general alumni reunions.
  - Annual Banquet, 1889-1951
    Invitations, menus, correspondence and other materials, including some guest lists, for the alumni annual dinner.
    - Annual Banquet, 1889 (Box 7, Folder 122)
      Copies (x2) of report from "The Cincinnati Commercial Gazette" (May 2, 1889) on the first banquet of the Xavier Alumni Association.
    - Annual Banquet, 1890 (Box 7, Folder 123)
      Newspaper article concerning the 1890 "Jubilee Week" celebration, including the Alumni Mass and Banquet, from the "Xavier University News--Centennial Supplement" (25 Sep 1940)
    - Annual Banquet, 1892 (Box 7, Folder 124)
    - Annual Banquet, 1894 (Box 7, Folder 125)
    - Annual Banquet, 1895 (Box 7, Folder 126)
    - Annual Banquet, 1896 (Box 7, Folder 127)
    - Annual Banquet, 1897 (Box 7, Folder 128)
    - Annual Banquet, 1898 (Box 7, Folder 129)
    - Annual Banquet, 1899 (Box 7, Folder 130)
    - Annual Banquet, 1900-1901 (Box 7, Folder 131)
    - Annual Banquet, 1902-1903 (Box 7, Folder 132)
    - Annual Banquet, 1904-1905 (Box 7, Folder 133)
    - Annual Banquet, 1906-1907 (Box 7, Folder 134)
    - Annual Banquet, 1908-1909 (Box 7, Folder 135)
    - Annual Banquet, 1910-1911 (Box 7, Folder 136)
    - Annual Banquet, 1912-1913 (Box 7, Folder 137)
    - Annual Banquet, 1914-1916 (Box 7, Folder 138)
    - Annual Banquet, 1924 (Box 7, Folder 139)
    - Annual Banquet, 1925 (Box 7, Folder 140)
    - Annual Banquet, 1926 (Box 8, Folder 141)
    - Annual Banquet, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 142)
    - Annual Banquet, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 143)
    - Annual Banquet, 1929 (Box 8, Folder 144)
    - Annual Banquet, 1930 (Box 8, Folder 145)
    - Annual Banquet, 1931 (Box 8, Folder 146)
    - Annual Banquet, 1932-1933 (Box 8, Folder 147)
    - Annual Banquet, 1934-1935 (Box 8, Folder 148)
    - Annual Banquet, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 149)
    - Annual Banquet, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 150)
    - Annual Banquet, 1941-1942 (Box 8, Folder 151)
    - Annual Banquet, 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 152)
    - Annual Banquet, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 153)
    - Annual Banquet, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 154)
    - Annual Banquet, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 155)
    - Annual Banquet, 1950-1951 (Box 8, Folder 156)
  - Graduate Receptions, 1897-1908
    - Graduate Receptions, 1897-1908 (Box 8, Folder 157)
      Notifications and correspondence relating to the annual reception for the graduating class.
  - Communion Breakfast, 1940-1941
    - Communion Breakfast, 1940-1941 (Box 8, Folder 158)
      Papers and correspondence relating to the Communion Breakfast held on March 23, 1941
  - Universal Communion Sunday, 1952-1995
    Correspondence, programs and papers relating to the annual Universal Communion Sunday events.
    - Universal Communion Sunday, 1952-1955 (Box 8, Folder 159)
    - Universal Communion Sunday, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 160)
    - Universal Communion Sunday, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 161)
    - Universal Communion Sunday, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 162)
    - Universal Communion Sunday, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 163)
    - Universal Communion Sunday, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 164)
    - Universal Communion Sunday, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 165)
    - Universal Communion Sunday, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 166)
    - Universal Communion Sunday, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 167)
    - Universal Communion Sunday, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 168)
    - Universal Communion Sunday, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 169)
    - Universal Communion Sunday, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 170)
    - Universal Communion Sunday, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 171)
    - Universal Communion Sunday, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 172)
    - Universal Communion Sunday, 1970-1972; 1975; 1977 (Box 9, Folder 173)
    - Universal Communion Sunday, 1992-1993; 1995 (Box 9, Folder 174)
  - Alumni Mailings, 1925-1954; 1997
    - Alumni Mailings, 1925-1954; 1997 (Box 9, Folder 175)
      Notifications sent to alumni, relating to the quarterly meetings of the Association and other events staged.
  - Lecture Series, 1895-1935
    Correspondence, notes and invitations relating to the Alumni Association's annual lecture series.
    - Lecture Series, 1895-1905 (Box 9, Folder 176)
    - Lecture Series, 1924-1932 (Box 9, Folder 177)
    - Lecture Series, 1933 (Box 9, Folder 178)
    - Lecture Series, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 179)
    - Lecture Series, 1935 (Box 9, Folder 180)
  - Father Hubbard Lecture, 1933
    - Father Hubbard Lecture, 1933 (Box 9, Folder 181)
      Papers, correspondence and publicity material for the lecture held in December 1933 by the Alumni Association featuring Father Bernard J. Hubbard, "The Glacier Priest."
    - Father Hubbard Lecture (1/2), 1934-1935 (Box 9, Folder 182)
    - Father Hubbard Lecture (2/2), 1934-1935 (Box 10, Folder 183)
      Publicity material and newspaper clippings relating to Father Bernard J. Hubbard, "The Glacier Priest."
  - San Francisco Earthquake Benefit, 1906
    - Events: San Francisco Earthquake Benefit, 1906 (Box 10, Folder 184)
      Papers relating to the Alumni Association's benefit staged to help Jesuit colleges in California damaged by the 1906 earthquake.
  - Luncheon Club, 1936
    - Events: Luncheon Club, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 185)
      Lists of attendees and other papers relating to the Alumni Luncheon Club.
  - "The First Legion", 1938; 1951
    - Events: "The First Legion", 1938; 1951 (Box 10, Folder 186)
      Correspondence, publicity material and financial records relating to the Alumni production of "the First Legion."
  - Dad's Club, 1941-1975
    - Dad's Club, 1941-1975 (Box 10, Folder 187)
      Papers relating to the Dad's Club of Xavier University, including regulations, lists of directors, and material relating to the annual conferences of the club.
  - Retreat Lists, 1950s
    - Retreat Lists, 1950s (Box 10, Folder 188)
      Lists of alumni attending retreats
  - Family Day, 1954-1995
    - Family Day, 1954-1995 (Box 10, Folder 189)
      Programs and publicity material for Family Day.
  - Parents Club, 1978; 1980
    - Parents Club, 1978; 1980 (Box 10, Folder 190)
      Brochures about the Parents Club and its activities and the 1978 Octoberfest event.
  - Events: Washington's Birthday, 1895-1910; undated
    - Events: Washington's Birthday, 1895-1910; undated (Box 10, Folder 191)
      Papers and correspondence relating to Washington's Birthday celebrations staged by the Alumni Association.
  - Events: Miscellaneous, 1891-2001
    - Events: Miscellaneous, 1891-1896 (Box 10, Folder 192)
      Papers and correspondence relating to events staged by the Alumni Association, including "Shakespearean Scenes" (1891), "Columbian Banquet" (1892), and a reception dedicated to Archbishop W. H. Wheeler (1896).
    - Events: Miscellaneous, 1905-2001 (Box 10, Folder 193)
      Papers and correspondence relating to miscellaneous social, sporting and educational events.
  - Local Chapter Events: Miscellaneous, 1941; 1995-2002
    - Local Chapter Events (Miscellaneous), 1941; 1995-2002 (Box 10, Folder 194)
      Programs and publicity material for miscellaneous events staged by local chapters of the Alumni Association.
  - Annual Chapter Leader Conference, 1957-1974
    Papers, correspondence and programs for the annual conference for leaders of local chapters of the Alumni Association. Typically, the conference program lists members of the Association Board of governors and local chapter officers, as well as providing information on the association at a national and local level, such as financial details, results of fund-raising efforts, etc. Also usually provides information about the Xavier campus, such as a map, and information on new development.
    - Annual Chapter Leader Conference, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 195)
    - Annual Chapter Leaders Conference, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 196)
    - Annual Chapter Leaders Conference, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 197)
    - Annual Chapter Leaders Conference, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 198)
    - Annual Chapter Leaders Conference, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 199)
    - Annual Chapter Leaders Conference, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 200)
    - Annual Chapter Leaders Conference, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 201)
    - Annual Chapter Leaders Conference, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 202)